- 大家好    - 你好
- Hey, guys.    - Hey.
- 你好   - 你好
- Hi.    - Hey.
我们有事要跟你们说
Uh, we need to talk about something.
对 我们今年不想主办感恩节晚餐
Yeah. We don't feel like we can host Thanksgiving this year.
- 什么？ - 你们开什么玩笑？
- What?    - Are you kidding?
因为领养的过程和压力
Well, it's just with work and the stress of adoption...
已经让我们精疲力尽了
...we don't feel like we have the energy.
还有 每年都要我们扛重担 并不公平
Plus, we don't think it's fair that every year the burden falls on us.
这不像是你会说的话
That doesn't sound like you.
是摩妮卡在说话
That's Monica talking.
不 我们一起决定的
No, no. We made this decision together.
她把话塞进你嘴里
She's putting words in your mouth.
不要把话塞进别人嘴里 只准塞火鸡
Don't you put words in people's mouths. You put turkey in people's mouths.
真不敢相信 这是艾玛的第一个感恩节
I can't believe this. This is Emma's first Thanksgiving.
- 才不是   - 不是？她什么时候出生的？
- No, it's not.     - It's not? When was she born?
我个人认为让你休息一下也不错
Well, personally, I think it's great you're giving yourself a break.
- 谢谢 菲比   - 当然 这样也好
- Thank you, Pheebs.     - Sure. It's just as well.
反正去年很糟 她的厨艺已经大不如前了
I mean, last year wasn't very good. I think she's losing her touch.
- 什么？你真是大错特错 小姐   - 是吗？真的？
- What? You are way off, lady.     - Am I? Really? Am I?
不如你煮感恩节晚餐向我证明
Well, why don't you cook Thanksgiving dinner and prove me wrong.
想像一下 你可以超越去年的表现
Well, think about it. You'd be trying to top what you did last year.
这是一场自我之间的桃战
You'd be in competition with yourself.
我最爱这种挑战
That's my favorite kind.
好 我煮定了
Okay, we are doing this.
不要这么容易就受到控制
Don't let yourself get manipulated this way.
少插手 钱德 这是我和我之间的事
Stay out of this, Chandler. This is between me and me.
我们应该一起做决定
We are supposed to make these decisions together.
你没看我录给你 菲尔医生的节目？
Did you not watch the Dr. Phil I taped for you?
- 你好   - 感恩节快乐
- Hey.     - Hi. Happy Thanksgiving.
"不吃肉的火鸡杀生节"快乐
Oh, yeah. Happy Meatless Turkey-Murder Day.
我在布立克街的店里订了巧克力派
You guys, I ordered some chocolate pies from that bakery on Bleeker.
- 你们可以帮我去拿吗？ - 你没有自己做？
- Could you pick them up for me?     - You're not making the pies?
我不做巧克力派
No, I don't make chocolate pies.
我小时候参加过吃派大赛
When I was younger, I entered this pie-eating contest.
我吃到光用想的就会吐
I ate so many that the thought of them makes me sick.
那你有赢得比赛吗？
Did you at least win the contest?
2分钟内吃12块派 还有盘子的一部分
Two minutes, twelve pies and a part of one tin.
- 四点见了   - 等不及了
- Okay, I'll see you guys at 4.    - Can't wait.
这顿晚餐绝对会棒透了 接招吧 去年的我
This dinner is gonna be so great. In your face, last-year me.
- 瑞秋？ - 什么事？
- Hey, Rach?     - Yeah.
艾玛今天有何行程？
Um, what's Emma doing today?
我想想 她要见她的律师
Well, let's see, uh, I know that she has a meeting with her lawyer...
还有拉一大沱屎
...and then she has to make a very big poop.
- 怎么了？ - 我想让她参加宝宝
- Why?     - Well, I want to enter her...
选美大赛
...in a baby beauty pageant.
天啊…这是我听过最诡异的事
Oh, my God. That's the creepiest thing I've ever heard.
拒绝之前先听我说 我朋友苏珊要带小孩参加
Okay, but before you say no, my friend Suzanne is entering her kid.
跟艾玛比起来 她真是丑毙了
And compared to Emma, she's a real dog.
- 菲比 小婴儿都很可爱   - 好吧
- Agh. Phoebe, all babies are beautiful.     - Oh, okay.
菲比 我只是觉得 让婴儿之间互相比较
No. Ugh, Phoebe, just the idea of pitting one baby against another...
争夺谁比较可爱 只为了一座奖杯…
...I mean, you know, and judging who's cuter just for a trophy...
还有一千美金 我对此事很有兴趣
And a thousand dollars. ...is something I'm very interested in.
拜托 别告诉罗斯
Oh, please, do not tell Ross.
他还是认为头脑比较重要
He still believes that what's on the inside is important.
好 艾玛需要穿女牛仔装比赛
Okay. Oh, and Emma needs a cowgirl outfit for the competition.
感恩节我要去哪找女牛仔服装？
Where am I gonna get a cowgirl outfit on Thanksgiving?
- 我是想…   - 把乔伊的
- Well, I was thinking...     - Take the clothes...
甘蓝菜娃娃的衣服脱掉
...off Joey's Cabbage Patch Kid! - Yeah!
有人又掉了指挥棒？
Did someone drop the baton again?
干嘛大老远从堪萨斯 跑来这做这种事？
Why come all the way from Kansas to do that?
不只宝刀未老 还历久弥坚
I don't get older, I just get better.
你知道我想到什么吗？
You know what just occurred to me?
这可能是我俩最后一次的感恩节
This could be our last Thanksgiving just the two of us.
可能很快就有宝宝了
I mean, we could be getting a baby soon.
- 还不确定   - 定有人会挑中我们
- You don't know that.      - Somebody's gonna pick us.
可是收养中心一点消息都没有
But we haven't heard a thing from the adoption agency.
相信我 一定会成功的
I'm telling you, it's gonna happen.
明年 就有你 我和小海明威宾
Next year, it's gonna be you, me and little Hemingway Bing.
- 干嘛？他是我最爱的作家   - 举出他任何一本书
- What? He's my favorite author.     - Name one of his books.
《黑色豪门企业》？
The Firm?
我看看 火鸡在炉子里 馅料也准备好了
Okay, let's see. Okay, the turkey's in the oven. The stuffing is ready.
你每次都自己煮 今年让我来帮忙
You know, you always cook this meal all by yourself. Let me help this year.
钱德 你真贴心
Oh, Chandler, that's sweet.
但不必菲尔医生说什么都照做
But you don't have to do everything Dr. Phil tells you to do.
我说真的 让我帮忙 不必像火鸡那种重要的东西
I'm serious, let me do something. Just not the turkey. Nothing high-profile.
我想想…对了 小红莓酱
Okay, let's see. Oh, the cranberry sauce.
简单做 而且没人会在乎
It's easy to make, and no one really cares about it.
继续说
Tell me more.
我要去对面 你先洗这些
I'm gonna go check on something across the hall. You start by washing these.
不要用洗洁精
Not with soap!
显然你没吃过我的棕榄马铃薯
You obviously haven't tasted my Palmolive potatoes.
- 你猜乔伊手上有什么？ - 三张今天游骑兵的票
- Hi. Hey, guess what Joey has.   - Three tickets to today's Rangers game!
- 老兄 我要他用猜的   - 哦
- Dude, I wanted him to guess.     - Oh.
- 天啊   - 没错 而且座位很棒
- Oh, my God.      - Yeah, they're great seats too.
- 你猜在座位在哪里？ - 场中间
- Guess where they are.     - Center ice.
我得罪你了吗？
Did I do something to you?
- 比赛一点才开始  - 那又如何？
- Mm. The game's at 1.     - So?
- 四点就要吃晚餐 会来不及   - 我们可以先离开
- Dinner's at 4. We'll never make it back.     - We leave before it's over. We'll be back.
现在这样说 但回来可能会很花时问
You say that, but it could take us a long time to get home.
而且 乔伊可能会迷路 我们还要回头去接他
Plus, Joey could get lost and they could have to page us to go pick him up.
拜托 只发生过两次
Dude, two times that happened!
听着 摩妮卡忙了一整天
Look, Monica's been working hard all day.
她本来不想主办的 我们不能去
She didn't want to host in the first place. We shouldn't go.
他说得对
He's right, man.
- 好吧 四点见了   - 好
- Yeah, I guess. So we'll see you at 4.     - Okay.
准备好享用我的特制小红莓
And get ready to taste my very special cranberries.
或者应该说"钱德莓"
Or should I say "Chan-berries"?
这笑点有点不足 老兄
That's some gentle comedy, dude.
我们还是要去看比赛吧？
We're still going to the game.
- 当然   - 当然
- Yeah.    - Yeah.
第16号参赛者 扬克斯来的蕾贝嘉霍普
This is contestant number 16, Rebecca Hope from Yonkers.
- 你好   - 菲比 我们该走了
- Hey.     - Phoebe, listen, I think we gotta go.
这地方太诡异了
This place is freaking me out.
那边有个家伙 我看他根本没有带小孩来
I've been watching this guy over there. I don't think he came with a kid.
我们不能现在离开
But we can't leave now.
本来有个宝宝 海莉 很讨评审欢心
There was this one baby, Haley, who was favored to win...
可是她得了喉炎不能来
...she got croup, so she had to stay home.
我们简直是不战而胜
This competition just blew wide-open, folks.
菲比 真的太怪了
Phoebe, it's just too weird.
我刚看到穿着吊带裤袜的一岁小孩
I just saw a 1 -year-old run around with pantyhose on.
我知道 应该要多费心思准备的
Oh, I know. We should've been more prepared.
没关系 现在看来 唯一的敌手的是卡麦隆
It's okay. Now, the way I see it, our real competition now is Cameron.
天啊 他们把她的衣服脱掉了
My God, they just took her sweater off.
瞧那对臂膀 你好 米其林宝宝
Look at those arms. Hello, Michelin Man.
- 菲比   - 哇哦
- Oh, Phoebe.    - Whoo-hoo.
走吧 已经三点了
Come on! You know what, it's already 3:00.
根本还没轮到艾玛这组 我们还得去吃晚赛
They haven't even gotten to Emma's group yet. We got dinner.
可是艾玛的实力坚强 她绝对会过关斩将
But Emma's got what it takes. She could go all the way!
- 菲比 冷静点   - 好
- Phoebe, you have to calm down.     - Ahem. Okay.
瑞秋 三州最辣的宝宝都在这里
Rachel, the hottest babies in the tri-state area are in this room right now.
我偷听到一个评审说 没有一个人比得上艾玛
I overheard one judge say that not one of them holds a candle to Emma.
- 真的？ - 当然
- Really?     - Yeah.
- 他真的这么说？ - 对
- You heard him say that?     - Yeah.
好吧…我们让这些小鬼哭着回家
All right. Okay. All right, let's give these babies something to cry about.
很好 来办正事 艾玛需要化妆
Good. Let's get down to business. Emma needs some makeup.
什么？
What? No... What?
不然她会白得跟鬼一样
She's gonna look washed-out next to the others.
不行 我不能让你替我的宝宝化妆
No, I'm not letting you put makeup on my baby.
- 为什么？ - 因为我已经帮她化了
- Why not?     - Because I already did.
（纽约游骑兵队季票）
（麦迪逊花园广场）
- 烂死了   - 滚出去 白痴
- Oh! You bum! Get off the ice!     - You suck! Get off the ice, you idiot!
- 比赛真精彩   - 没错
- What a game.     - I know. Yeah.
- 钱德错过这场比赛真可惜   - 他没来真可惜
- I can't believe Chandler's missing this.     - I'm sorry he's not here.
可是我得说有椅子放零食真好
But I gotta say, I am really enjoying nacho chair.
对 如果你不要一直 把我的手打掉会更好
Yeah, I'd probably enjoy it more if you didn't keep batting my hand away.
哦
Oh!
- 太好了   - 这座位真棒
- Yeah!     - These seats are great.
没错…我上次来看《冰上假期》
I know, I know. When I was here for "Holidays on Ice"...
坐得太后面 关颖珊都看不到我的看板
...I was sitting so far away, Michelle Kwan couldn't read my banner.
我们该走了 不然要迟到了
Whoa, we'd better get going. If we don't leave now, we're gonna be late.
可是现在打成平手 迟到又如何 女生们会先到
But it's a tie game. So we're a little late. The girls will be there.
等再得一分再走
Let's just stay for one more goal.
- 我不知道   - 等他们打群架
- I don't know.     - One more fight.
- 好   - 那好
- Okay.     - Okay.
人到哪去了？已经迟到45分钟了
Where is everybody? They're 45 minutes late.
他们竟然没来 我做牛做马都是为了谁？
I can't believe they're not here. I slave and I slave for what?
他们毁了小红莓节
They've ruined Cranberry Day.
- 多晚了？ - 45分钟
- How late are we?     - Forty-five minutes.
- 拿去   - 好
- Wow.     - Here.
好
Yeah. Okay.
瑞秋和菲比已经到了 他们应该先开动了
Rachel and Phoebe are already there, so they probably started without us.
我们只要溜进去 没有人会过问我们到哪了
We could just slip in, and no one needs to know where we were.
- 你最好拿下假手指   - 想得美…
- You may want to lose the foam finger.     - Oh, no, no, no.
你休想拿去戴
You just want to put it on your hand.
- 嘿   - 哦
- Hey.    - Oh.
你们没去吃感恩节晚餐？
You...? You're not at Thanksgiving?
- 不   - 没有 我们迟到了
- No.     - No, we're late.
- 你们在这做什么？ - 我们也迟到了
- What are you doing here?     - We're late too.
我们以为你们会准时 所以迟到应该无妨
We figured we could be late because you'd be on time.
不要指着我 姓崔的
Don't point that thing at me, Tribbiani.
- 没人到？摩妮卡会杀了我们   - 你们到哪去了？
- Nobody's here? Monica's gonna kill us.     - Yeah, where were you?
- 这个…   - 还有 奖杯哪来的？
- Well... Uh...     - Yeah, what's with the trophy?
- 额   - 我们去参加拼字比赛
- Uh, well, uh...    - We were at a spelling bee.
而且我赢了
And I won.
你赢得感恩节成人拼字比赛冠军？
You won an adult Thanksgiving Day spelling bee?
是的 是…的 是的
Yes. Y-E-S. Yes.
给我看…
Let me see this.
"纽约区小宝贝冠军"？
"Grand Supreme Little Darling, New York Division"?
就是本人
That's me. Heh.
你让艾玛参加选美？
You entered Emma in a beauty pageant?
而且她似乎有化妆
And it looks like she put makeup on her.
等等…这件女牛仔装 怎么那么眼熟？
Wait a second. Where have I seen that cowgirl outfit before?
真是的 她是我们的女儿
I can't believe this. She's our daughter.
你把她当展示狗 真是罪不可赦
That you would treat her like some kind of show dog is inexcusable.
- 她赢了一千美金   - 一年只办一次吗？
- She won a thousand dollars.     - So this is an annual thing?
这是艾莉西亚美的衣服
That's Alicia May Emory's outfit!
各位 里面有人不太高兴
Guys, there are people in there who are not getting any happier.
- 我们该怎么办？ - 先进去
- What are we gonna do?     - Figure it out.
我要先带艾玛去睡午觉
I gotta put Emma down for a nap.
瑞秋 待会顺便帮 艾莉西亚美穿点衣服
And, Rach, while you're in there, throw something on Alicia May.
- 好吧 我们该说什么？ - 哦
- All right, what are we gonna say?     - Ooh!
就说我们被抢劫
We'll say that we were mugged.
对被抢劫的人会有恻隐之心
You can't get mad at someone who's been mugged.
很好 可是你看起来不像被抢过
Good. But you don't look like you were mugged.
这样
No. Here.
拜托
Hey!
你有听到声音吗？
Do you hear something?
他们在外面
They're out there.
给我看
Let me see.
真不敢置信 迟到一小时
I can't believe this. They're an hour late...
还站在外面聊天
...and they're just standing out there talking.
看出去的世界都扭曲了 乔伊的手变得好巨大
Everything's so distorted. It looks like Joey has a giant hand.
上面写着"游骑兵" 他们跑去看比赛
That says "Rangers" on it. They went to the game.
这下他们不得好死了
Oh, they are in for a world of pain.
- 罗斯的衣服破了   - 他们既迟到又衣衫不整
- Ross' shirt is torn.     - They're late and they're sloppy.
好 艾玛睡了 你的衣服怎么了？
All right, Emma's napping. What happened to your shirt?
我被抢劫 口袋被抢走
I got mugged, and they stole my pocket.
我们在找搪塞的藉口
We're just trying to figure out an excuse.
不如这样…
Hey, ooh! How about this?
可以说摩妮卡说五点 不是四点 这样刚好准时
We could say that Monica told us 5:00, not 4:00. That way we're right on time.
或者…
Or!
可以在公寓里放毒品 再报警告发她
Or we could plant PCP in the apartment and call the cops on her.
好一个解决掉藏毒的好方法
That would be a good way to get rid of all the PCP we have lying around.
就说她说五点
We'll just say that she said it was 5:00.
装没事 我们没迟到 是准时到达
We'll just act casual. We're not late, we're right on time.
"我们知道你们在外面"
"We know you're out there."
会是谁写的？
Who do you think it's from?
天啊 真是糟透了
Oh, God, this is bad. This is so bad.
我们就进去面对他们
Well, let's just go in there and face them.
我不要先进去 摩妮卡的额头上会爆青筋
I'm not going in first. I bet that vein on Monica's forehead is popping like crazy.
那最恐怖了 活像一条闪电
I hate that thing. It's like a bolt of lightning.
不如猜拳决定
I have an idea. Why don't we play Rock, Paper, Scissors.
输的人先进去
Whoever loses, goes in first.
- 好 来吧   - 好了吗？
- All right, I'm in.     - Ready.
我赢了
Ha, ha! I win.
- 那是什么？ - 这是火 它可是所向无敌
- What is that?     - That's fire. It beats everything.
真的？它比水球强吗？
Oh, really? Does it beat water balloon?
- 噗   - 啊
- Pop-pssh.     - Aw.
算你行 菲比布非 算你行
Well-played, Phoebe Buffay. Well-played.
算了 我们一起进去
All right, let's all go in at the same time.
- 好吧   - 好
- Okay.     - Okay. Okay.
- 锁住了   - 什么？现在才锁起来
- It's locked.     - What? Oh, sure, now they lock it.
当他们在沙发上做爱时 感觉像
When they're having sex on the couch, it's like:
"欢迎来看我毛得惊人的屁股"
"Come on in, my butt is surprisingly hairy!"
好了 别这样 两位 很抱歉我们迟到了
All right, come on. All right, you guys, we're so sorry we're late.
让我们进去 我们一起吃晚餐
Please let us in so we can have dinner together.
不 食物都冷了 火鸡干了 馅料也糊了
No, everything's cold. The turkey's dried out and the stuffing's all soggy.
没错 那碗小红莓酱也…
Yeah, and there's a bowl of cranberry sauce that's...
小红莓酱怎么了？
What happens to cranberry sauce?
- 没事 它还好好的   - 感谢老天爷
- Nothing, it's fine.     - Oh, thank God.
别这样 两位 对不起 我们的地铁故障了
Come on, you guys, we're sorry. Our subway broke down.
你说谎 你们去看比赛 我看到乔伊的手
That's a lie! You went to the game. I can see Joey's hand.
看在老天份上 快脱掉
For the love of God, take it off!
两位 迟到原因不重要 我们现在都来了
Guys, it doesn't matter why we're late. We're all here now.
拜托让我们进去享用你美味的火鸡
Please let us in so we can have some of your delicious turkey.
我梦过传真机也有这种功能
I had a dream once about a fax machine that did that.
你们只能吃那些火鸡
That's all the turkey you're gonna get.
- 要怎么决定谁吃？ - 水球
- How are we gonna decide who gets this?     - Water balloon!
怎么办？我快饿死了
What are we gonna do? I'm starving.
我想起来了 还有东西吃
Ah, oh! I just remembered, we do have something to eat.
摩妮卡早上有放东西在炉子里
Monica put something in our oven this morning.
你敢去就会后悔一生
You touch that, and you will be sorry!
各位 最好听她的 我没见过这么大的青筋
Guys, I'd listen to her. The vein is bigger than I've ever seen it!
- 啊   - 哈哈哈
- Ah!     - Ha-ha-ha.
天啊 是球芽甘蓝
Oh, my God, it's Brussels sprouts!
我宁愿饿死
That's worse than no food.
你们只有摩妮卡的臭球芽甘蓝
Ha, ha! All you got was Monica's stinky Brussels sprouts.
臭？
Stinky?
请不要赶我出去
Please let me stay on this side of the door.
我知道了 我还有旧钥匙
Oh, I know! I still have my old key.
- 哦   - 可以用来开门
-  Oh.     - We can just unlock the door.
这样好吗？ 他们已经不想见到我们了
I don't know if that's a good idea. They don't wanna be with us.
我也不想见到他们
I don't wanna be with them either...
可是感恩节 不想在一起也要在一起
...but it's Thanksgiving, and we should not want to be together together.
如果我可以进去当面道歉
If I could just get in there, make a face-to-face apology.
看着他们的眼睛 他们一定会原谅我们
Look them in the eye, I could get them to forgive us.
- 真的吗？ - 我说真的
- I don't know.     - I'm telling you...
我办得到
...I can do it.
没错 他办得到
Yeah, he can do it.
啊
Oh...
食物好丰盛
Aw. It all looks so beautiful.
- 火鸡 馅料…   - 还有小红莓
- The turkey, the stuffing.     - The cranberries.
够了 连猴子都会做
Ugh, enough! A monkey could've made them.
两位 听我说 我们真的很抱歉
Hey, listen, guys, we feel really terrible.
他又在使眼色了
He's doing that weird eye-contact thing.
不要看他…
Don't look at him. Don't look at him.
别这样 两位 我们真的…很抱歉
Come on, you guys. We want you to know we're very, very sorry.
对吧？各位
Right, guys?
- 我很难过   - 对不起
- I feel terrible.     - Oh, so sorry.
我们不要毁了这一天 你这么辛苦
But let's not ruin this day. You've worked so hard.
不如既往不究一同愉快的用餐好吗？
Let's move past this and try to have a nice meal all together, huh?
漂浮人头说得有理
The floating heads do make a good point.
对 他们的确也不好受
Yeah, they do seem to feel pretty bad.
- 好难过   - 真不好受
- So bad.     - So bad.
真不好受
So bad.
好吧
Okay.
你们去拿甜点 我就让你们进来
Okay, you two go get the dessert, and I'll let you in.
甜点？
Dessert?
我叫你和菲比去拿派 没有忘记吧？
Yeah, I asked you and Phoebe to pick up the pies. You did remember, right?
派…我以为你说"奖品"
Pies. Oh, we thought you said "prize."
拿去
Here.
- "小宝贝冠军"？ - 恭喜
- "Grand Supreme Little Darling"?     - Congratulations!
天啊 你们忘记拿派？我真不敢相信
Oh, my God, you forgot the pies? Well, I cannot believe this.
你们逼我煮饭 却迟到一小时
You forced me to make dinner, you're an hour late...
现在连这么小的事都忘记
...and you forget the one little thing that I asked you to do.
女孩们 看你们干的好事
Really, girls, not cool.
你们男人头也好不到哪去 你们偷跑去看比赛
Well, you man-heads aren't any better. You lied about going to the game.
明明知道会迟到 还是照样去
You knew it'd make you late, and you went anyway.
我有点不耐烦了 我们道歉都说过了
Hey, I'm getting a little tired of this. We said we're sorry.
今天是感恩节 应该要宽恕他人
It's Thanksgiving, for Pete's sakes! A day of forgiveness.
- 是感激他人   - 不要逼我上去揍你
- It's a day to be thankful.     - Don't make me come up there!
道歉太迟了
It's too late for apologies.
好 我们走 我不吃你的蠢晚餐
Fine, let's just go. I don't need your stupid dinner.
如果你不流口水的话 会比较具说服力
That would be a lot more convincing if you weren't drooling.
- 那是口水？ - 抱歉
- Ew, is that what that is?     - Sorry.
各位 我们自己去过感恩节
Come on, you guys, let's just do our own Thanksgiving.
- 我来做菜   - 我们出去吃
- Yeah, I'll cook.     - Yeah, let's go out.
嘿
Hey!
祝你们三个感恩节快乐
Yeah, you three have a nice Thanksgiving.
- 三个？ - 对 你 钱德和青筋
- The three of us?     - Yeah. You, Chan and the vein.
- 我被卡住了   - 乔伊 这招不管用
- Uh-oh. I'm stuck.     - Joey, that is not gonna work.
我说真的
No, seriously. Unh.
- 我被卡在这里了   - 我拉你出来
- I'm really wedged in here.     - I'll pull you through.
好
Okay.
停…这样脑部可能会受损
Ow! Stop, stop, I'm worried about damaging my head.
现在担心太迟了
It's a little late for that.
快点 想法子帮我
Hurry up, you gotta do something.
好吧 但情况还是不变
All right, well, this does not change anything.
我们要拿东西润滑他的脸
We need to get something to grease his face.
- 有火鸡油   - 去拿
- We got turkey grease.     - Bring it.
我很抱歉 把青筋拟人化
I just want to say that I'm sorry I referred to the vein as a separate person.
来吧
Here you go.
好香
Oh, that smells good.
- 好了吗？ - 好 试试看
- Okay?     - Okay, try it.
没有用
Gah! It isn't working.
- 看来得把链条解开   - 快 我的耳朵没感觉了
- We're gonna have to unscrew the chain.     - Hurry, I can't feel my ears.
你的耳朵曾经有感觉吗？
Can you ever feel your ears?
好问题
Interesting.
- 钱德 你的工具在哪？ - 我放在推土机上
- Chandler, where are your tools?     - Oh, I left them on my bulldozer.
我哪来的工具？
I don't have tools.
- 我有 可是瑞秋借去了   - 我借给罗斯
- Well, I do, but Rachel borrowed them.     - I lent them to Ross.
- 我拿给乔伊   - 我放在公园里
- I gave them to Joey.     - I left them at the park.
我真想趁现在整整他
I'm finding it really hard not to mess with him.
我已经把球芽甘蓝塞到他裤子里
I stuffed Brussels sprouts down his pants.
好主意
Nice.
我得去接电话
Okay, I have to get that.
等我回来 我要你和你的朋友消失
Now, when I get back, I want you and your friends to be gone.
感恩节结束了 青筋说的
Thanksgiving is over. The vein has spoken.
- 越来越痛了   - 听着 我把门拉开
- It's really starting to hurt.     - Look, I'm gonna pull on the door...
你们用谁的 也许会有空间让他挤出去
...and you guys push. Maybe we can get enough room to wiggle him out, okay?
好 开始推
Okay, so push.
等等 我们玩得正开心
Just a sec. We're kind of in the middle of something here.
不要塞东西到我的裤子里
Ooh, ooh. Stop putting things down my pants.
- 快点 各位 推    - 对 快推
- Come on, guys, push!   - Yeah, come on, push!
用力堆…
Push! Push!
- 我的小红莓   - 老天 我身上都是食物
- My cranberries!     - Man, I got food all over me.
看你干的好事 摩妮卡会杀了你
I can't believe what you did. Monica's gonna kill you.
你看…漂浮人头干的好事
Look! Look! Look what the... Look what the floating heads did!
我不在乎
I don't care.
发生什么事？
What's going on?
是收养中心打来的
That was the adoption agency.
然后？
And?
- 我们有宝宝了   - 你说真的？
- We're getting a baby!     - Are you serious?
俄亥俄州有个孕妇选中我们
There's a pregnant woman in Ohio, and she picked us.
- 天啊 太好了   - 真是太好了
- Oh, my God, that's great!     - That's incredible.
真替你们高兴
I'm so happy for you.
今年感恩节比其他都棒
This Thanksgiving kicks last Thanksgiving's ass!
敬摩妮卡和钱德 还有俄亥俄州那孕妇
To Monica and Chandler and that knocked-up girl in Ohio.
真高兴你们终于有宝宝了
I'm just so happy you guys are finally getting a kid.
没错 有想过让她参加选美吗？
I know. Have you considered pageanting?
真不敢相信他们打来 我们真的要有宝宝了
I can't believe they called. I mean, we're actually getting a baby.
我能感同身受
Aw. I know how you feel.
- 真的？ - 当然
- Really?     - Sure.
我和艾莉西亚美也经历同样的过程
I went through the exact same thing with Alicia May Emory.
一切等持和不确定成…
The waiting, the wondering.
然后有一天 玩具反斗城打电话来
Then one day, I get that call from Toys"R"Us.
她刚好有货
She was in stock.
果真一模一样
That is the exact same thing.